export const lvl6 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What is the most famous landmark in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane City Hall',
      'B) Sydney Opera House',
      'C) Melbourne Town Hall',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane City Hall',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What iconic bridge connects Fortitude Valley and the city center?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Story Bridge',
      'B) Sydney Harbour Bridge',
      'C) Golden Gate Bridge',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Story Bridge',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `Which park is located at the heart of Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Roma Street Parkland',
      'B) King George Square',
      'C) South Bank Parklands',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Roma Street Parkland',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What is the name of the popular beach near Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Surfers Paradise', 'B) Moreton Island', 'C) Noosa Heads'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Moreton Island',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What museum in Brisbane is known for its indigenous art?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Queensland Museum',
      'B) Gallery of Modern Art (GOMA)',
      'C) Australian Museum',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Gallery of Modern Art (GOMA)',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What famous clock tower is located in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Big Ben',
      'B) Brisbane City Hall Clock Tower',
      'C) Sydney Town Hall Clock',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane City Hall Clock Tower',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What historical building is located in the city center?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Old Government House',
      'B) Parliament House',
      'C) State Library of Queensland',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Old Government House',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What structure is a popular venue for concerts and events in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Convention Centre',
      'B) Brisbane Exhibition Centre',
      'C) Brisbane Performing Arts Centre',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane Convention Centre',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `Which botanical garden is located in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Botanic Gardens',
      'B) Sydney Botanic Gardens',
      'C) Melbourne Botanic Gardens',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane Botanic Gardens',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What is the tallest building in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Skytower',
      'B) Q1 Tower',
      'C) Empire State Building',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane Skytower',
  },
];
